{
        "HTMLQuiz": [     
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question_type": "MC",
          "question": "Which of the following is the current HTML standard??",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "HTML",
            "optionb": "HTMLX",
            "optionc": "HTML5",
            "optiond": "HTML4"
          },
          "correct_answer": "C",
          "explanation": "The current standard for HTML is HTML5"
        },
        
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question_type": "MC",
          "question": "All HTML code must be nested within which of the following tags??",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "html",
            "optionb": "page",
            "optionc": "doc",
            "optiond": "div"
          },
          "correct_answer": "A",
          "explanation": "All HTML code must be nested within a html tag"
        },
        
        {
          "id":3,
          "question_type": "MC",
          "question": "The acronym HTML stands for which of the following?",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "Hyper Take Maker Language",
            "optionb": "Hyper Token Marker Language ",
            "optionc": "Hypertext Markup Language",
            "optiond": "Hyper Textmarkup Language"
          },
          "correct_answer": "C",
          "explanation": "HTML stands for Hypertext Markup Language"
        },
        
        {
          "id":4,
          "question_type": "TF",
          "question": "Multiple radio buttons in the same group can be set to a checked state at the same time",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "True",
            "optionb": "False"
          },
          "correct_answer": "B",
          "explanation": "Only one radio button in the same group can be in the checked state at a time"
        },
        
        {
          "id":5,
          "question_type": "Fill In",
          "question": "Which tag represents a numbered list?",
          "correct_answer": "ol",
          "explanation": "ol stands for 'ordered list' which can be rendered as a numbered list"
        },
        
        {
          "id":6,
          "question_type": "TF",
          "question": "Tables can be used to position text and images",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "True",
            "optionb": "False"
          },
          "correct_answer": "A",
          "explanation": "A table is a good way to organize text and images in different positions"
        },
        
        {
          "id":7,
          "question_type": "MC",
          "question": "How many different heading elements does HTML support?",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "1",
            "optionb": "3",
            "optionc": "6",
            "optiond": "12"
          },
          "correct_answer": "C",
          "explanation": "HTML can support 6 different heading elements"
        },
        
        {
          "id":8,
          "question_type": "TF",
          "question": "A text editor creates the HTML code for you as you add elements to the Web Page",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "True",
            "optionb": "False"
          },
          "correct_answer": "B",
          "explanation": "A text editor does not create the HTML code for you"
        },
        
        {
          "id":9,
          "question_type": "MC",
          "question": "What are two components of HTML attributes?",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "Name, Value",
            "optionb": "Amount, Title",
            "optionc": "Call, Sign",
            "optiond": "In, Out"
          },
          "correct_answer": "A",
          "explanation": "Name and Value are components of HTML attributes"
        },
        
        {
          "id":10,
          "question_type": "Fill In",
          "question": "Which tag can be used to add a paragraph?",
          "correct_answer": "p",
          "explanation": "p initiates a paragraph"
          },
          
        {
          "id":11,
          "question_type": "MC",
          "question": "According to the W3C recommendation, what's the appropriate way of indenting nested HTML elements?",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "1 space",
            "optionb": "2 spaces",
            "optionc": "2 tabs",
            "optiond": "All of the above"
          },
          "correct_answer": "B",
          "explanation": "The recommended way of indenting is 2 spaces "
        },
        
        {
          "id":12,
          "question_type": "TF",
          "question": "video clips are unlikely to have a large file size",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "True",
            "optionb": "False"
          },
          "correct_answer": "B",
          "explanation": "Video files tend to be large in file size"
        },
        
        {
          "id":13,
          "question_type": "TF",
          "question": "CSS considers every HTML5 element to be enclosed in a line",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "True",
            "optionb": "False"
          },
          "correct_answer": "B",
          "explanation": "CSS considers every HTML5 element to be enclosed in a box"
        },
        
        {
          "id":14,
          "question_type": "MC",
          "question": "A family of styling specifications with a common name is called a:",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "Class",
            "optionb": "Group",
            "optionc": "Flock",
            "optiond": "Family"
          },
          "correct_answer": "A",
          "explanation": "A family of styling specifications with a common name is called a Class"
        },
        
        {
          "id":15,
          "question_type": "Fill In",
          "question": "The preferred way to specify a break that continues the text on the next line in a Web page is?",
           "correct_answer": "br/",
          "explanation": "br/ is the recommended way to specify a break "
          },
        
        {
          "id":16,
          "question_type": "Fill In",
          "question": "To create a Web page with a list of HTML commands and their tags, it would be best use:",
          "correct_answer": "A definition list",
          "explanation": "A definition list the best way to create a web page with a list of HTML commands and their tags"
        },
        
        {
          "id":17,
          "question_type": "Fill In",
          "question": "The tags used to specify table headings/column headings are:",
          "correct_answer": "th",
          "explanation": "th is the tag used to specify table/column headings"
        },
        
        {
          "id":18,
          "question_type": "TF",
          "question": "Microsoft Explorer is an example of an open source browser",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "True",
            "optionb": "False"
          },
          "correct_answer": "B",
          "explanation": "Firefox is an example of an open source"
        },
        
        {
          "id":19,
          "question_type": "Fill In",
          "question": "Computer experts call spaces that have been inserted for readability",
          "correct_answer": "white space",
          "explanation": "Computer experts call spaces that have been inserted for readability: white space"
        },
        
        {
          "id":20,
          "question_type": "TF",
          "question": "The width of a line of text on a Webpage is determined by the size of the text used",
          "options": {
            "optiona": "True",
            "optionb": "False"
          },
          "correct_answer": "B",
          "explanation": "The width of a line usually depends on the size of the browser window. It also depends on the screen resolution"
        }
     ]
}
